<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris J Wilson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ChrisJWilson&quot;&gt;@ChrisJWilson on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 13:44:07 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 13:44:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We have tears in our eyes
As we wave our goodbyes,
We so loved being with you, we three.
So do please now and then
Come and see us again,
The Giraffe and the Pelly and me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodbye #ISC18LX 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/984bb93a38.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;3C730A74-48F8-4066-86F0-938B4BF75078.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 13:43:43 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/23/we-have-tears.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/23/we-have-tears.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/8028093ca3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/8028093ca3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/0d26b07658.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/0d26b07658.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lettering practice with &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/rohdesign&quot;&gt;@rohdesign&lt;/a&gt; and @claire_ohl at #ISC18LX love nesting little letters here and there.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 09:21:08 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/22/lettering-practice-with.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/22/lettering-practice-with.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Take the first step</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a session at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sketchnotecamp.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;International Sketchnote camp in Lisbon&lt;/a&gt; today I felt challenged and excited to share more of my sketchnoting online. It’s something I’ve resisted doing because I don’t feel I’m as good as others and I know that there are sometimes mistakes in my sketchnotes: crooked lines, spelling, running out of space. I was, however, reminded of the value of &lt;strong&gt;sharing your work&lt;/strong&gt; as you go along and that, in reality, the process is what is really of value not the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But how could I start? What step would be the easiest to get me to share more of my sketchnotes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my case, this would be &lt;strong&gt;taking the photo of the sketchnote to share&lt;/strong&gt;. If I don’t take the picture, I’ve got nothing to share. Once I’ve taken the photo then I’ve got something to share and it’s fairly simple to type out a note and share the sketchnote from there. But taking the photo is a hanging point for me. I often don’t take my phone out, and when it is I forget to/ resist take the photos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, even if I don’t share a sketchnote after photographing it, immediately or after a wait, I still have the sketchnote save and more available to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this applied to many other areas. Just doing the first step can get the process going.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 00:03:51 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/22/take-the-first.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/21/take-the-first.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Putting Makayla Lewis’s lesson in to action and sharing my work from #isc18lx 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ef2f42b5bd.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;75EF616E-E846-4FEF-AC7E-1033EC025761.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 12:47:47 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/21/putting-makayla-lewiss.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/21/putting-makayla-lewiss.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The Mac Sparky Shortcuts Field Guide [Mini Review]</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just finished the &lt;a href=&quot;https://learn.macsparky.com/p/siri&quot;&gt;MacSparky Shortcuts Field Guide&lt;/a&gt; 
My tldr; it’s great for people new to workflow/shortcuts and those who have one or two but never really make their own and want ideas. 
If you’ve made a shortcut with multiple apps and variables before, this is probably not for you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 16:11:46 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/19/the-mac-sparky.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/19/the-mac-sparky.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://gender-decoder.katmatfield.com/&quot;&gt;Gender decoder for jobs&lt;/a&gt; interesting tool that checks if your job ad has gender biased language.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 11:43:36 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/19/gender-decoder-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/19/gender-decoder-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Currently reading: &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/books/9780060891541&quot;&gt;On Writing Well&lt;/a&gt; by William Zinsser 📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 10:11:06 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/19/currently-reading-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/19/currently-reading-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Cleaning Up Workflows</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the release of Shortcuts, I cleared out about 70% of my old Workflows in preparation. There were about two or three groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Workflows I just never use. In some cases the apps went away or their functionality was replaced with iOS improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Workflows I replaced with better ones&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Workflows I downloaded to see what the creator had done even though I had no use for them. 
At the same time I also moved my most used workflows to the top of the app and organized some of the workflows near similar ones. I.e. I have a book review and movie review workflow for DayOne, they are next to each other now along with other DayOne workflows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could have done this at any time but this was the prompt I needed. Maybe I’ll make this a regular thing especially with the experiments I’ve been doing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:07:58 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/18/cleaning-up-workflows.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/18/cleaning-up-workflows.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I finally moved from TextExpander legacy to a subscription. I’ve had issues with syncing snippets for a while and yet I use this tool so often it’s worth paying for its support.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 08:54:23 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/18/i-finally-moved.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/18/i-finally-moved.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Should We Stop Listening to Podcasts? — CJ Chilvers 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cjchilvers.com/blog/should-we-stop-listening-to-podcasts&quot;&gt;Should We Stop Listening to Podcasts? — CJ Chilvers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When you mention time and attention theft, most creators think of Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram (which I call Facebook II). They usually don’t think about Youtube or podcasts, which have the same issues: the ad model and all its abuses to the listener, and the lack of quality in favor of burn-out-inducing “consistency” and quantity (something that is also tied to the ad model).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently cut the number of podcast I listen to for similar reasons. With exceptions, podcast tend towards entertainment over content. I don’t think there is anything inherently wrong with that. &lt;strong&gt;It’s good to switch off and be entertained from time to time but not all the time.&lt;/strong&gt;
Still greater intentionality is always good, as is &lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/09/protect-your-attention.html&quot;&gt;protecting your attention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 19:24:22 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/17/should-we-stop.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/17/should-we-stop.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Really excited to be finally downloading shortcuts. Let’s see what this baby can do!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 19:22:12 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/17/really-excited-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/17/really-excited-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/YULPUe0vgWA&quot;&gt;Austin Kleon on the Sketchbook Skool Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I think a lot of that side hustle stuff comes from the economic pressures of the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 13:01:53 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/17/austin-kleon-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/17/austin-kleon-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Emulsify Camera from Sean Harding (Like shooting black and white film)</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/emulsify-camera/id1408272207?mt=8&quot;&gt;Emulsify Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tested this app by &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/sharding&quot;&gt;@sharding&lt;/a&gt; for a couple of weeks and it’s not like your typical iPhone camera app. It isn’t feature rich but it has strong opinions. It is influenced by the classic experience of shooting black and white film, with two iconic film simulations, but does so in a non typical way. Most camera apps aim to show you want you are going to see in the end result, Emulsify recreates the unpredictability of film in that you see things in colour before getting your Black and white results. This means you have to train your eye a bit to think about shades and tone and not just colour differences. 
It’s a very different camera app experience that I suspect some won’t like, but personally I’m hooked. That’s perhaps less surprising considering the amount of black and white film I’ve been burning through recently. Now I just need to get a new iPhone to test the camera on that…you know…to help Sean.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:42:37 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/17/emulsify-camera-from.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/17/emulsify-camera-from.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished Reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0374105863/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Arbitrary Stupid Goal: Tamara Shopsin&lt;/a&gt; 📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 18:35:44 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/16/finished-reading-arbitrary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/16/finished-reading-arbitrary.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Since Apple Pay (finally) came to Poland I’ve been really pleased with it, espeically on the watch. But the last week or two has shown me how great Apple Pay on the Web is. It’s much easier than many other systems. ( Need to remember the danger of ease leading to spending more).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 16:27:52 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/16/since-apple-pay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/16/since-apple-pay.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>I’d rather be a blogger – Paul Jarvis 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pjrvs.com/blogger/?mc_cid=aa65d786c3&amp;amp;mc_eid=d098183321&quot;&gt;I’d rather be a blogger&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I just think one of the main reasons that the internet took off like it did from the late–90s onward was that people could finally have a voice, regardless of whether or not that voice drove clicks and views. No need to go through gatekeepers like print publications, book publishers, etc… we could just write something and hit publish. Now our voices are collectively passed through the values of content marketing and growth-hacking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I probably could have linked to Paul’s whole article but what’s the point in that. So instead I quoted the part I found most inspiring. It’s a really great take on the difference between blogging and content marketing. This hit me hard as I’ve done a lot of “contentting” and not that much blogging until I came on Micro.blog…it’s good to be blogging.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 16:10:42 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/16/id-rather-be.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/16/id-rather-be.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>FART for better photos - Ken Rockwell </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://kenrockwell.com/tech/fart.htm&quot;&gt;Fart for better photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I take my best pictures when I FART first.
FARTing helps us remember to make a strong, meaningful photo instead of just snapping away and winding up with a lot of boring, thoughtless snapshots.
FART is a mnemonic for a creative process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ken Rockwell is not the best photographer in the world and some people really disagree with him on some aspects of photography but this little mnemonic is great photography advice for everyone. I love starting here rathe than “the rule of thirds” or whatever because all of those composition rules can be broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought of this post as I had seen that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cjchilvers.com/blog/finally-a-photography-101-course-i-can-recommend&quot;&gt;CJ Chilvers had written in support&lt;/a&gt; of the upcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://thesweetsetup.com/capturing-a-great-photo-on-iphone/&quot;&gt;The Sweet Setup Photo course&lt;/a&gt;.
Honestly, when they announced they were making photo course I was worried. The feel I usually get from tech journalists who write photo advice focus more on the tech side of photos (surprise). So they’ll really get into the &lt;em&gt;“need”&lt;/em&gt; for a super fast lens, getting a tone of bokeh and finally some classic composition tips like “the rule of thirds” (all of which can be broken). But CJ Chilvers isn’t that type of photographer and he focuses on photos for the average person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what made me think of this post. It’s great for a complete beginner taking their first photo, but it’s also a useful reminder for a more seasoned hand who knows all the “composition rules”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 18:25:28 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/15/fart-for-better.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/15/fart-for-better.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Siri Shortcuts and DayOne…that could potentially be interesting&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 18:01:39 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/15/siri-shortcuts-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/15/siri-shortcuts-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So iOS 12 is out but Siri Shortcuts isn’t out yet 😩&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 20:17:41 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/14/so-ios-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/14/so-ios-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;iOS 12 is here! 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ffe8f079f3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;EF92B196-24A1-4369-A64C-DFDEF7250407.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 17:11:37 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/14/ios-is-here.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/14/ios-is-here.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>How Maria Popova starts a blog post. </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I noticed something about Brain Picking’s blog posts that made me investigate. It was the curious way Maria chose to start her post. By splitting a quote in two and referencing the writer in the middle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The most regretful people on earth,”&lt;/em&gt; Mary Oliver wrote in her beautiful reflection on the central commitment of the creative life, &lt;em&gt;“are those who felt the call to creative work, who felt their own creative power restive and uprising, and gave to it neither power nor time.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brainpickings.org/2018/09/14/walt-whitman-on-creativity/&quot;&gt;Walt Witman on Creativity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a great way to kick of some writing as it creates an “open loop” where you want to know the answer to the end of the quote. I wondered if she does this all the time as I recognised the style, and sure enough I found a post from a few days before with the same style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Everything can be taken from a man,” Holocaust survivor Viktor Frankl wrote in his timeless treatise on the human search for meaning, “but one thing: the last of the human freedoms — to choose one’s attitude in any given set of circumstances, to choose one’s own way.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brainpickings.org/2018/09/10/toni-morrison-beloved-freedom/&quot;&gt;Toni Morrison on the Deepest Meaning of Freedom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it is not the only way she kicks of a post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The pioneering naturalist John Muir held the poetic conviction that when we look closely at any aspect of our world, “the whole universe appears as an infinite storm of beauty.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brainpickings.org/2018/09/12/ryota-kajita-ice-formation/&quot;&gt;Japanese Artist Ryota Kajita’s Otherworldly Photographs of Ice Formation in Alaska&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here she starts with the description and places the quote in full. The key difference, it’s a shorter quote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless Maria certainly seems to like her quotes to kick off her posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:34:52 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/14/how-maria-popova.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/14/how-maria-popova.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;the number of companies who sent me emails saying that I &lt;strong&gt;had&lt;/strong&gt; to update my preference to keep getting emails post GDPR (I didn’t ) and  then kept emailing me is not insignificant.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:19:09 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/14/the-number-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/14/the-number-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you let any website give you push notifications? I see requests so often and I’m wondering if anyone actually accepts (and if there are any occasions when it might even be good!) The only one I can imagine ever accepting is my favourite blog and even then I’d prefer RSS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:33:42 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/14/do-you-let.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/14/do-you-let.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pca.st/wx7I&quot;&gt;Do by Friday takes on GTD - Early Beta 🎧 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This episode was a truly great one and while humors, it’s a great overview of some key (and useful) GTD principles. I’ve just scheduled a weekly review for the end of the work day AND I’m planning a mind dump as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 09:51:05 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/14/do-by-friday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/14/do-by-friday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Cognitive Dissonance for Marketing 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/psychology-secrets-for-marketing/cognitive-dissonance-704ada47b048&quot;&gt;Cognitive Dissonance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It has also been observed that if a person finds themselves engaging in activities which are in opposition to what they believe, they will be &lt;strong&gt;more willing to change their belief or adopt new beliefs to suit the situation, rather than change their actions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m researching for an article and this statement really struck me. People will change their beliefs to match their actions more than change their actions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 14:12:09 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/13/cognitive-dissonance-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/13/cognitive-dissonance-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Reading Aloud - Austin Kleon 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://austinkleon.com/2018/09/12/reading-aloud/&quot;&gt;Reading aloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I find that reading my work aloud makes it weird enough that I can’t scan or gloss over anything.
Reading to an audience is best, because you start really judging the thing when you have to project it into a room full of people. Quentin Tarantino says he likes to read his scripts to his friends, not for their feedback, but their presence. “I don’t want input, I don’t want you to tell me if I’m doing anything wrong, heavens forbid,” he says, “But I write a scene, and I think I’ve heard it as much as I can, but then when I read it to you … I hear it through your ears, and it lets me know I’m on the right track.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use this trick with proofreading texts. Sometimes I have to look at the same thing that’s been sent back and forth about five times, often with a minor change introduced that is easily missed. Reading aloud is one of the only ways to keep my eyes fresh.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 11:31:23 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/13/reading-aloud-austin.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/13/reading-aloud-austin.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Me: Well I don’t think these iPhone speak to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me five minutes later: That’s it! I’m definitely getting the iPhone Xs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me another five minutes later: Hum, maybe the iPhone Xr is a real bargain…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;repeat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 08:50:56 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/13/me-well-i.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/13/me-well-i.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>What makes a good blog - Merlin Mann</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.43folders.com/2008/08/19/good-blogs&quot;&gt;What makes a good blog?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As I think about the blogs I’ve returned to over the years – and the increasingly few new ones that really grab my attention – I want to start with, ironically enough, a list. Here’s what I think helps make for a good blog.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Merlin Mann&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just discovered this thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ismh&quot;&gt;@ismh&lt;/a&gt; ‘s &lt;a href=&quot;https://512pixels.net/2018/09/10-years-of-512-pixels/&quot;&gt;ten years of 512 pixels&lt;/a&gt; post and I’d say every bit of it still applies today. Both posts are worth reading.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 16:32:31 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/12/what-makes-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/12/what-makes-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Hoping to Be Delighted by Apple</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well it’s Apple iPhone event day and I feel conflicted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m really ready for a phone upgrade, I want to pass my current phone on to my wife&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; so we can share Live Photos of my daughter, plus then she won’t have a terrible battery life. But I feel a bit nervous. &lt;strong&gt;I’m worried Apple won’t give me a reason to upgrade today.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a funny fear to have, that someone &lt;strong&gt;won’t&lt;/strong&gt; make you want to give them money. No doubt I’ll change my mind as they could probably just release a phone with a new processor and I’d want to upgrade but at the same time I’m really not sure where they go next with smartphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I’m intrigued by the idea of a foldable phone and I suspect something like a Samsung note that can unfold into a small square tablet with stylus could be very interesting. But that doesn’t seem on the horizon for Apple. Then again it is not unlike Apple to quietly work away at something for a while and then suddenly release it upon the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, I’ll be watching the keynote (or more likely checking the summary afterwards) and hoping that there will be a surprise or two that I don’t see coming. Apple are often good at delivering those sweet hardware and software features that delight and perhaps the iPhone Xs will see some new delight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For the record, I’d buy her a new phone but she is very resistant to spending money on herself. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:24:05 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/12/hoping-to-be.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/12/hoping-to-be.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/f807d0c114.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/f807d0c114.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/a4adc7f8a3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/a4adc7f8a3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finished my last notebook last night and starting a new one today. Trying a different (cheaper) brand but designed for sketching. Let’s see.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:46:19 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/12/finished-my-last.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/12/finished-my-last.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So I just set up Microsub on my microblog using aperture and downloaded indigenous on my iPhone. Time to take this baby for a spin.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:45:54 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/11/so-i-just.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/11/so-i-just.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;the &lt;a href=&quot;http://monday.micro.blog/2018/09/10/episode-vasta.html&quot;&gt;Micro Monday cast with&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/vasta&quot;&gt;@vasta&lt;/a&gt; is really interesting and worth considering and reflecting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 14:24:03 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/11/the-micro-monday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/11/the-micro-monday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://experimentwithnature.com/03-found/experiment-with-paper-how-to-make-a-one-page-zine/#.W5dtZ5MzbOQ&quot;&gt;How to make a one-page zine&lt;/a&gt;
Thanks to Austin Kleon for this one. Now I just need to grab some paper and make my zine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 11:11:42 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/11/how-to-make.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/11/how-to-make.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/d9ff04a463.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/d9ff04a463.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;height: auto;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Testing &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/sharding&quot;&gt;@sharding&lt;/a&gt; ‘s emulsify app at one of the spots I pass everyday and find useful for testing contrast. The blacks are crushed a bit more than the default camera app but it has a nice style.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 09:07:48 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/11/testing-sharding-s.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/11/testing-sharding-s.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Education Needs to Be Inconvenient</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seths.blog/2018/09/education-needs-to-be-inconvenient/&quot;&gt;Education needs to be inconvenient&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Education needs to be inconvenient because it relies on effort and discomfort to move us from where we were to where we want to be. The internet gives us more access than ever, and if we care enough, we can use that convenient access to explore the inconvenient places that we know we should be exploring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seth Godin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:46:28 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/10/education-needs-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/10/education-needs-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was trying to write an article and it just &lt;em&gt;wasn’t&lt;/em&gt; coming. The ideas were all jumbled and the thought wasn’t clear or refined. So I finished, and then &lt;em&gt;“published”&lt;/em&gt; to DayOne. I love having a place to send writing that isn’t online for things which are too private or incomplete.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 09:53:40 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/10/i-was-trying.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/10/i-was-trying.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Discussion starter…what is the correct/your way of assembling lasagna? (Yes I just cooked lasagna)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 20:14:58 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/09/discussion-starterwhat-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/09/discussion-starterwhat-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Protect your attention</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I made this sketch in my commonplace book about a week and a half ago and since then this idea has come up a few times for me (including the latest Episode of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hellointernet.fm/podcast/108&quot;&gt;Hello Internet &lt;/a&gt;. That’s usually a sign to take notice of an idea, when it keeps coming up. It’s also part of the value of a commonplace book, you can notice the themes and ideas that come up again and again and see patterns and connections emerging over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attention is one of our most valuable resources and yet nowadays it feels like it’s given away for so little. Even giving away your Email address for some freebie is an invitation to take some of your attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve made a few changes recently to try and protect my attention more but I know that I both don’t stick to all of those changes and they don’t go far enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Focusing on longer and deeper content&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;planning silence&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;limiting disctration time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ve all helped but the issue persists. Today I disabled some more notifications, removed another couple of podcasts from my app and finally set some limits in the new screen time settings in iOS 12. I hope they’ll help, but I know the attitude is the most important step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/7d8b339f1d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;421&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 19:30:53 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/09/protect-your-attention.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/09/protect-your-attention.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Thai Rolls </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ecccd07ce2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ecccd07ce2.jpg&quot; width=&quot;450&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/de43c41c1c.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/de43c41c1c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;450&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d never heard of Thai rolls before but it’s a type of ice cream that basically gets made in front of your eyes. We went for kinder bueno with coconut pieces. Pretty tasty.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 20:23:12 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/08/thai-rolls.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/08/thai-rolls.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Since my daughter was born there has been a massive increase in my use of Live Photos… coincidence? I think not.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 20:03:39 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/07/since-my-daughter.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/07/since-my-daughter.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Looks like you can browse the old discover articles in iOS 12 now.The question is have they restored this feature or is it a beta bug?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 16:13:28 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/07/looks-like-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/07/looks-like-you.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A few times I’ve asked a question and people have said “hey, where did you find that” most of the time it’s from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://help.micro.blog/archive/&quot;&gt;help page archive&lt;/a&gt; well worth a check for little things you may have missed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 15:53:11 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/07/a-few-times.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/07/a-few-times.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen a load of articles about “iPad only photo workflows” where I always think “We’ll that’s fine if you take 10 photos”. &lt;a href=&quot;https://fujilove.com/working-on-the-move-what-is-the-lightest-and-most-compact-solution/&quot;&gt;This article is the first which I thought would work for a professional.&lt;/a&gt; with proper backups and file management.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 14:13:40 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/07/ive-seen-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/07/ive-seen-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night I found myself playing with halide (as it was very low light). The darkroom integration is pretty interesting so now I’m checking out &lt;a href=&quot;https://thesweetsetup.com/shooting-editing-great-photos-halide-darkroom/&quot;&gt;this sweet setup post&lt;/a&gt; in using halide and darkroom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 09:21:28 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/07/last-night-i.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/07/last-night-i.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Currently Reading : &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0374105863/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Arbitrary Stupid Goal: Tamara Shopsin&lt;/a&gt; 📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 19:32:15 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/06/currently-reading-arbitrary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/06/currently-reading-arbitrary.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Steal Like The Decemberists</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pca.st/episode/f0742c5d-ba50-4313-a2bf-ebe6271b3ade&quot;&gt;Song Exploder - the Decemberists : once in my life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As I was just playing it and playing it over and over again, it reminded me of one of these Yo La Tengo songs called “Barnaby hardly working” which is one of my favourite songs of all time. So we were playing it live and I felt moved one night to sing the last two lines of “Barnaby hardly working”, “lays down by the river, face down by the river”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colin Meloy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I loved this episode because it’s such a great example of “stealing like an artist”. Referencing the influences that lead to the song but how this diverse group of influences lead to a completely different song that doesn’t sound like the influences at all.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 16:35:53 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/06/steal-like-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/06/steal-like-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.relay.fm/penaddict&quot;&gt;Pen Addict&lt;/a&gt; Kickstarter kit arrived. Now which pens to fill it with 🤔
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/a993a857cc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;D0D3C666-6DFC-4C7F-B595-2E58EEF85F51.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 21:16:53 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/05/my-pen-addict.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/05/my-pen-addict.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>On Writing Your Job on Your About Page</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I realised that I could add an about page to my Micro.Blog blog and it could be longer than the mini about desciption in my Micro.blog profile (thanks &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/simonwood&quot;&gt;@simonwood&lt;/a&gt;). As I was writing it, I did the classic thing that I’ve heard the folk at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theminimalists.com/do/&quot;&gt;The minimalists podcast&lt;/a&gt; complain about. &lt;strong&gt;I used my job title to describe myself&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In facts, I used my job title as my &lt;strong&gt;primary&lt;/strong&gt; description of myself. This is the natural and expected course of action. When we meet someone new, one of the first few questions is usually &lt;em&gt;“and what do you do?”&lt;/em&gt; which really means _“What’s your job?” and potentially, “how much do you earn and are you worth my time”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, the second part is the highly cynical take from the minimalists which I somewhat agree with. At the same time, if you do a 9-to-5 job, the chances are you spend 1/3 of your day doing that thing (then a further third sleeping) meaning you probably do spend most of your time doing your job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My last job was a teacher, it’s a pretty well respected thing to include in your profile. People generally think teachers are okay but not necessarily useful for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My new job is a title I really like, &lt;strong&gt;“Content Writer”&lt;/strong&gt; which is a way to say &lt;em&gt;“copywriter but we pay you less”&lt;/em&gt; and it reflects a lot of what I like doing, researching and write. But in truth, it’s not a full representation of my character and what I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I tried a different &lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/about/&quot;&gt;About page&lt;/a&gt; here, one that focuses on actions and personality traits I want to exhibit first rather than where my paycheck comes from. I’m sure I’ll revisit it and update it, but it’s a start.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 15:16:50 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/05/on-writing-your.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/05/on-writing-your.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Evernote lost its CTO, CFO, CPO and HR head in the last month as it eyes another fundraise | TechCrunch</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2018/09/04/evernote-lost-its-cto-cfo-cpo-and-hr-head-in-the-last-month-as-it-eyes-another-fundraise/&quot;&gt;Evernote lost its CTO, CFO, CPO and HR head in the last month as it eyes another fundraise | TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;TechCrunch has learned and confirmed that in the last month, Evernote  lost several of its most senior executives, including its CTO Anirban Kundu, CFO Vincent Toolan, CPO Erik Wrobel and head of HR Michelle Wagner beyond the usual attrition of engineers and designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The departures are coming at a key time: we have also heard that Evernote is fundraising, potentially in a down-round from its most recent (but now several years-old) valuation of $1.2 billion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yikes! This is really not great news. I’ve used Evernote for years and been a paying member for the last three. It’s not a perfect app/service, but it does the job and in the last year the company has really improved (aka, they stopped bugging me about workchat). Still, stuff like this suggests that things may not be so hot, I’d better look for an alternative and a way to move all my notes out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 22:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/04/evernote-lost-its.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/04/evernote-lost-its.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But I was opposed to becoming “mileage crazy”. Mileage craziness is a serious condition that exists in many forms. It can hit unsuspecting travellers while driving cars, motorcycles, riding in planes, crossing the country on bicycles or on foot. The symptoms may lead to obsessively placing more importance  on how many miles are traveled than on the real reason for traveling. 
… &lt;strong&gt;A person must be very careful to not be overly concerned with arriving&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/006095955X/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;A Walk Across America&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 19:15:02 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/04/but-i-was.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/04/but-i-was.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
