<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris J Wilson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ChrisJWilson&quot;&gt;@ChrisJWilson on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 09:02:58 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 09:02:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m really enjoying these weekly link things that some people are doing on MB. It’s great for discovering something interesting and I almost always check them unlike email newsletters which are full of links. Maybe it feels less obligatory to click through or it’s the mindset I’m in 🤷‍♂️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 09:02:07 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/10/080207.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/10/080207.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;David Sparks’s Omnifocus Field Guide is very good. Especially the custom perspectives, I love some of the ideas he offers here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:58:35 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/07/david-sparkss-omnifocus.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/07/david-sparkss-omnifocus.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My techo arrived ☺️
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ee989ebbd1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;6EADE30F-29BE-4567-A409-DCF486E5D039.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:24:40 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/06/my-techo-arrived.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/06/my-techo-arrived.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Copywriter world problems. How do I say we are “low-cost” without sounding like we’re rubbish, or that we’re really expensive but pretending to be cheap (i.e. affordable pricing). Probably overthinking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:19:03 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/06/copywriter-world-problems.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/06/copywriter-world-problems.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My RSS service hunt seems to be leading me towards Inoreader at the moment and I’m trying the free version but I’m going to take a look at a couple of others before finally settling.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:48:29 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/06/my-rss-service.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/06/my-rss-service.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/47fe4bce9b.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/47fe4bce9b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;height: auto;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good morning&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:53:02 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/06/good-morning.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/06/good-morning.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got a blister from playing bass at the weekend and it looks like it’s just about okay to play guitar again. So tonight is learning to play jazz guitar night :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:11:14 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/05/i-got-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/05/i-got-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mission for today, buy an ugly Christmas sweater :D&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:02:51 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/05/mission-for-today.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/05/mission-for-today.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Facebook's had a bad year, but the users are staying.  </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.hubspot.com/marketing/facebook-2018-user-motivation&quot;&gt;Looking Back on Facebook’s Murky 2018: Here’s Why Users Are Sticking Around (New Data)🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But with every new announcement and report, it seems that it isn’t quite enough for people to part ways with the social network for good. After many of these events, we ran surveys to determine if it they were enough for users to delete or deactivate their accounts, and every time, there was a consensus: “No, I’ll stay.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This stuff depresses me and yet…I’m still technically on Facebook. There are a couple of groups I use there and I do some social media tasks for my church. I don’t really get value out it, certainly less than other places, and the value I do get out of it could be replaced by alternatives….and yet I’m still there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:01:57 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/04/facebooks-had-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/04/facebooks-had-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A copywriting course I’ve been following is much more a general business course. It’s not bad, it’s just mis-advertised and only covers the basics of copywriting while spending more time on general business points (which is not what I need).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:27:45 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/04/a-copywriting-course.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/04/a-copywriting-course.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s one AR app I use and I don’t know why I do. It’s a football app that lets you see the team lineups in AR. I could just look on a screen but I like walking round the teams. It’s pointless but I like it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:47:18 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/04/theres-one-ar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/04/theres-one-ar.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0735211299/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Atomic habits&lt;/a&gt; has really helped me understand the value of certain GTD practices like the weekly review. James mentions that the people with the “strongest self-discipline” actually just have the right systems in place so they don’t need to exercise self-discipline.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:20:55 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/03/atomic-habits-has.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/03/atomic-habits-has.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://brooksreview.net/2018/04/the-guru-trap/&quot;&gt;The Guru Trap 🔗 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep coming back to this post and thinking about it. My favourite Apple blogger’s/podcasters have other jobs because they give real examples (exception is Federicco Viticci).&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:20:29 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/12/03/the-guru-trap.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/12/03/the-guru-trap.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/39f051bf0e.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/39f051bf0e.jpg&quot; width=&quot;599&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;height: auto;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The frost yesterday morning.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:33:28 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/30/the-frost-yesterday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/30/the-frost-yesterday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Move Slow and Mend Things? 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://brooksreview.net/2018/11/building-technology-for-good/&quot;&gt;https://brooksreview.net/2018/11/building-technology-for-good/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’m not sure there is a clear answer, however my gut says that Facebook is more net negative than iPhone. I wonder how much of that could have been avoided if more consideration was given while building out the Facebook, as was given when Apple built iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an interesting link and comment by &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ben&quot;&gt;@ben&lt;/a&gt;  and I wanted to continue that thought by suggesting the opposite of Facebook’s approach. Move slow and Mend things. Take your time, consider the impact of your actions and the unintended negative side effects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder what this would also look like in my personal life. If I didn’t jump on the latest hype train but waited to let other -suckers- people test them out first and find the issues. If I were more critical of what I let impact my life than I currently am?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:26:22 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/29/move-slow-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/29/move-slow-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I signed up to a course to learn how to use a drawing app on the iPad better. I had a survey about why I signed up and most of the answers suggested that people want to learn about how to turn their art in to a business. I have no interest in that and it actually made completing the survey difficult! 
I understand the idea of trying to segment your course attendees and then up sell a business course (everything seems to have a premium turn your … into a business course now) but it really shocked me how “Of course you want to do this” it was this time. 
What’s wrong with doing something #justforfun&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:44:36 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/28/i-signed-up.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/28/i-signed-up.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://kottke.org/18/11/the-best-table-tennis-shot-of-2018&quot;&gt;The Best Table Tennis Shot of 2018 🔗 📹&lt;/a&gt;
One of those titles that sounds clickbaitey, but totally sticks the landing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 09:30:51 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/28/the-best-table.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/28/the-best-table.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>A Suggestion for Better Starbucks Cup Size Name</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Something I’ve been wondering about. Starbucks coffee size names.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are clearly influenced by Italian culture and attempt to communicate that but they are confusing so people just use large middle and small (in my experience). So it makes me wonder what could be a better system of names. Ones which reflect Italy but also are clear over the size.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Piccolo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Medio&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grande
I don’t think everyone would use them, but you wouldn’t have to remember that Vente is in fact the largest coffee size, not the grand grande.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:41:35 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/27/a-suggestion-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/27/a-suggestion-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Come for the Topic, Stay for the Hosts?</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember hearing Merlin Mann make this statement on back to work some five years ago or so. At the time I nodded my head in agreement, but recently I’ve been questioning this statement a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I initially accepted it as that had been my response with every podcast I listened to, I found them from the topic, but I stayed because I enjoyed the hosts views and the way they talked. In fact, I suspect one of my favorite podcasts of all time had a lot to do with the wonderful timbre of the main host’s voice. As further proof I could point to podcasts where I had tried but stopped listening to because I didn’t enjoy the hosts, and Bionic/bonanza which started as an android podcast but descended (well really ascended) into a podcast about secret volcano bases, Elon Musk’s plans to take over the world, round the world races and saved by the bell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But lately I have counter points. Podcasts where I enjoy the hosts (as I have/do listen to their other podcasts), but they have moved away from the original topic and so it no longer appeals to me. Or another podcast where I enjoyed these hosts talking about this topic but now they’ve moved into a more generic topic, they don’t seem to be as interesting or original.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I think Merlin’s statement is a great generalization, I now believe a great podcast is a combination of many factors including the topic, the hosts perspectives and views, their interaction off each other and technical factors like good sound recording.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:56:26 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/27/come-for-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/27/come-for-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Georgia On My Mind Playlist</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my new listening habits at work is to listen to a jazz classic performed by several different people. One of the best things about Jazz is how different performers interpret and add their own flare onto a standard version. YouTube is such a great place to find these variations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLykefMsqC1nda54r6js-w5tOFCc7YTCgd&quot;&gt;playlist of variations of Georgia on my mind&lt;/a&gt;, some more jazzy, some more bluesy, many are solo guitar pieces but some have backing tracking or a band.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.s. I’ve made a &lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/jazz-standards/&quot;&gt;new page where I’ll collect some of these lists.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:52:41 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/26/georgia-on-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/26/georgia-on-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the Google features that I find incredibly useful and very worrisome is maps telling you predicted busy hours and live results. I often use it to plan when I go to the shops, and yet it is so upfront about how Google is tracking you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 09:14:44 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/26/081444.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/26/081444.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>I still love paper </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In many ways I think my attachment for my smartphone is born out of my same attachment for notebooks and pens. The later preceded the former when my father gifted me a translucent purple covered a6 pocket notebook at high school. 
The point was to write my tasks and assignments so I wouldn’t have to rely on my very fallible memory and instead stay organized and on top of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason it stuck was because I also had a set of bright neon pens that I used to reimagine the cover and pages inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nethertheless, the notebook did it’s job and lead to a transformative moment in my life. I can divide my life into the disorganized forgetful mess I was before I had my first notebook, and the increasingly organizing and effective person I am still becoming since then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I went looking to get my first smartphone, the one feature I wanted was a good calendar so I could replace my paper one. I didn’t care about any games or the camera, they were of far lesser importance than the calendar and notes. To this day, my calendar, task manager and notes app are in my top five most used apps (the camera and podcast app are also present).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But despite the usefulness of these applications, there’s still something delightful about paper and pen. The blank page is a creative curse, but it can also be an inspiring invitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blank page can become a picture, a task list, a quick doodle for no reason, a profound quote to be remembered, or a brain dump of ideas and concerns regarding a project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As great as my iPad Pro and Apple Pencil are, they aren’t the same as a good pen and notebook.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 15:46:43 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/24/i-still-love.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/24/i-still-love.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My daughter has started teething…this is the darkest timeline.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 15:28:32 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/24/my-daughter-has.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/24/my-daughter-has.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My Black Friday shopping was finally buying the Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild. I held off buying it previously to encourage me to complete Mario Odyssey and then waited for a good deal. So far, It’s amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 09:00:13 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/24/my-black-friday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/24/my-black-friday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Outside of krakow station last night 
Not certain about the edit. Need to brush up on my lightroom skills. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/d8b9d7c51e.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;49102408-315C-47EB-98F6-5521C44AE630.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:40:01 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/22/outside-of-krakow.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/22/outside-of-krakow.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just wondering what service you use for RSS and why.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:29:24 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/22/just-wondering-what.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/22/just-wondering-what.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Go on an “Artist date”</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I made the image below inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.accidentalcreative.com/podcasts/ac/three-weekend-rituals-that-will-refresh-your-creativity/&quot;&gt;the accidental creative podcast&lt;/a&gt; this morning, which was itself inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://juliacameronlive.com/basic-tools/artists-dates/&quot;&gt;Julia Cameron&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/d6994a6307.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;B41DBC84-8292-4B54-8E0E-2222DD8EAC72.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:48:29 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/21/go-on-an.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/21/go-on-an.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The Annoying Trend of Making Stuff About Making Stuff</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the things that annoys me the most about the modern internet landscape is how much stuff is made about making stuff. Especially when it is the same form as the thing which is being made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Blog posts about writing blog posts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Youtube Videos about making YouTube videos&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Podcasts about podcasts (this is probably the least offender)
I now wonder if this is part of the inherit nature of being an indie creator. If you become successful and go full time, then the thing you are making becomes your full time job. What else can you write about…except writing about running your job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, &lt;strong&gt;it’s not inevitable&lt;/strong&gt; and I think the &lt;strong&gt;best&lt;/strong&gt; online content avoids this pitfall. CGP Grey’s great videos aren’t about how he makes his videos, Amanda Palmer’s music isn’t about making music and Andy Weir wrote a great book about a man on mars on his blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My challenge to myself is to focus more on making things, and not making things about making things.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 18:50:42 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/20/the-annoying-trend.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/20/the-annoying-trend.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine buying a WordPress theme with a “lifetime license”, now imagine not getting any updates in the last year and half after a few since it’s launch. NOW imagine there is a new version of that theme where you have to purchase a new “lifetime” license.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:06:27 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/20/imagine-buying-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/20/imagine-buying-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/AD-ZfN9tlDE&quot;&gt;Nate Lopez Performs “Georgia On My Mind” 🎵 📹 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some smooth acoustic blues for the afternoon&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 14:18:44 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/20/nate-lopez-performs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/20/nate-lopez-performs.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/e7f5c1710b.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/e7f5c1710b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;450&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;height: auto;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krakow train station tonight 📸&lt;br /&gt;Edited in darkroom for the iPad.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 20:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/19/krakow-train-station.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/19/krakow-train-station.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;iPhone photography discovery of the day 📷&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darkroom lets you edit the background and foreground of a portrait mode separately. That’s cool. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/fa2b1a9018.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;68EAECAE-4F12-4BF5-8BFD-7B50CF3564FA.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 17:21:12 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/19/iphone-photography-discovery.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/19/iphone-photography-discovery.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The digital divide is being flipped 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://seths.blog/2018/11/the-digital-divide-is-being-flipped/&quot;&gt;The Digital Divide is Being Flipped - Seths Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Today, as digital tools get cheaper and more widespread, a new gap is appearing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If a parent uses a tablet or a smartphone as a babysitter, it’s a lot easier to get a kid to sit still. As a result, parents who are busy, distracted or can’t afford to spend as much 1:1 time as they’d like are unknowingly encouraging their kids to become digital zombies, with a constant need for stimulation, who are being manipulated by digital overlords to click and click some more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past in Europe, pale skin was seen as attractive, as people who were suntanned worked in the fields. Now, the reverse is true as it is a sign of not working to have travel abroad and obtained your tan. This digital situation reminds me of getting tanned, the element which distinguished you in the past was access to the internet, now it is being able to disconnect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also see &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/1455586692/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Deep Work by Cal Newport&lt;/a&gt; (affiliate link)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:22:08 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/19/the-digital-divide.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/19/the-digital-divide.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;monday-morning-music---️&quot;&gt;Monday Morning Music  🎵 📽️&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1_6RQKoCTVY&amp;amp;feature=share&quot;&gt;Jeff Goldblum: Cantaloupe Island&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:49:10 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/19/074910.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/19/074910.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I Checked Lightroom CC when it came out and wasn’t &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; impressed. Back then I was using an iPhone SE. I downloaded it this weekend on my iPhone Xs and with the combination of new camera and improvements, it’s really a lot better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:42:47 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/19/i-checked-lightroom.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/19/i-checked-lightroom.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pca.st/episode/34cffef3-d044-4c62-9ff3-1679ad0821d3&quot;&gt;Yes, I am a tastemaker: The Pen Addict 334&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An episode even non-pen addicts may enjoy when Brad discusses his passion and realising his words can have an impact.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 12:27:59 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/17/yes-i-am.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/17/yes-i-am.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The whole “I’m passionate about the Oxford Comma” thing feels very cliche now. So my bio will have “No.1 em dash fan”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 14:01:45 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/16/the-whole-im.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/16/the-whole-im.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m really enjoying playing with the iPhone XS camera. It lets me take photos I couldn’t with the SE. Shot with &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/id357404131?at=10lu9G&amp;amp;ct=IPG&quot;&gt;Slow Shutter Cam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/154c95affc.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:17:52 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/16/im-really-enjoying.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/16/im-really-enjoying.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fontoplumo.nl/2018/11/15/new-twsbi-eco-trans-green-and-blossom-red-just-in-time-for-christmas/&quot;&gt;TWSBI ECO in trans green and Blossom Red for Christmas&lt;/a&gt; The green looks pretty cool.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 13:03:28 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/15/twsbi-eco-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/15/twsbi-eco-in.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Colder weather means porter time. This is a Christmas porter. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/0ffed7cdd7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1EA2A0BB-F78B-4CAB-89F3-6E04AE88380F.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 20:43:45 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/14/colder-weather-means.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/14/colder-weather-means.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pocketcasts 7. Great update.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:15:35 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/14/pocketcasts-great-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/14/pocketcasts-great-update.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Any wireless charging recommendations for iPhone Xs? I’m looking at the Anker PowerPort 5, The Logitech Powered for iPhone looks the best…but that price.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:05:50 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/14/any-wireless-charging.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/14/any-wireless-charging.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Being creative is not so much the desire to do something as the listening to that which wants to be done: The dictation of the materials” -Anni Alberts “Weaving in a college” via Austin Kleon’s Blog &lt;a href=&quot;https://austinkleon.com/2018/11/07/the-dictation-of-the-materials/&quot;&gt;“The Dictation of the Materials”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the whole thing, you won’t regret it.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 09:09:31 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/13/being-creative-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/13/being-creative-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally got my iPhone XS in a semi set state. Still moving a couple of items around by this is my homescreen for now. Might add this to my now page 🤔&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ca23fc36d6.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 18:32:22 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/12/finally-got-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/12/finally-got-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a public holiday here in Poland so I took my daughter down to the graduation tower connected to Wieliczka salt mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/747c9558b8.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:43:03 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/12/its-a-public.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/12/its-a-public.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In addition to Veterans Day and Armistice day, November 11 is &lt;strong&gt;Polish Independence Day&lt;/strong&gt;. Prior to the end of the First World War, Poland had faced 123 years under foreign rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/8f7205b932.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 07:54:55 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/11/in-addition-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/11/in-addition-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/82616224ff.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/82616224ff.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;height: auto;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morning coffee in krakow. The sign says “coffee is essential”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 12:35:35 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/10/morning-coffee-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/10/morning-coffee-in.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Morning Music 🎵 &lt;a href=&quot;https://song.link/s/6DDoFN7yNQmL2YXojqAk8S&quot;&gt;L.I.F.EG.O.E.S.O.N by Noah And The Whale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 09:21:16 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/09/morning-music-lifegoeson.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/09/morning-music-lifegoeson.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fulcrum-anglican.org.uk/articles/good-news-national-witness/&quot;&gt;Good News: National Witness? | Fulcrum Anglican&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Good liturgy isn’t everything, but bad liturgy isn’t anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tom Wright on the state of modern evangelical worship.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 07:38:56 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/09/good-news-national.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/09/good-news-national.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Where are the fresh blogging opinions 🔗</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macdrifter.com/2018/11/daring-fireball-dan-frakes-goes-to-apple-as-mac-app-store-editor.html&quot;&gt;Daring Fireball: Dan Frakes Goes to Apple as Mac App Store Editor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Cross linking between blogs has nearly dried up. It’s almost impossible to find new opinions because everyone links to the same three websites, like I’m doing now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A lot of voices have moved on to podcasting. Frankly, as someone that also podcasts, it’s easier and there’s less accountability than with blogging. Today, I also see a lot of thoughtful people writing on Discord groups. There’s little value in blogging unless you just like to practice writing in public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of those articles that starts discussing one issue, but the commentary actually is far more interesting than the inital discussion (In my opinion at least). I wonder how accurate Gabe’s prognosis is (that new voices are podcasting). While I see truth in this, I also think one of the issues is that online writing has become quite formulaic and people simply copy others ideas without offering something fresh. 
No one could be a full time blogger in the early days of online writing, now there are a host of them (and companies that employ writers) who’s opinions are well regarded. I’ve started (and stopped) following some new writers as I realised they were just repeating others points. At the same time, I have discovered fresh voices who offer something unique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rosemaryorchard.com/&quot;&gt;Rose Orchard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://beardyguycreative.com/blog/&quot;&gt;Denny Henke&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://decoding.io/&quot;&gt;Zsolt Benke&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gr36.com/&quot;&gt;Greg Morris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thedent.net/&quot;&gt;Andy Nicolaides&lt;/a&gt;
Admittedly some of those same voices also use their litteral voices for podcasts too, but that doesn’t stop the fact that they are adding their unique writing voice. Really, it’s not that writing is in decline, it’s that more writers are also professional podcasters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:05:27 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/11/08/where-are-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/11/08/where-are-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
