<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris J Wilson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ChrisJWilson&quot;&gt;@ChrisJWilson on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 21:02:34 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 21:02:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Four new pens to play with…I might be &lt;em&gt;starting&lt;/em&gt; to develop a problem. 
Left to right:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00PV7RMSA/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Lamy Joy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B002RJPLQK/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Pilot Parallel 6mm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B004ESZ9DW/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Pilot Parallel 3.8mm &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B005NXE8KC/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Uni chalk marker broad tip &lt;/a&gt;
Expect some sample pages in the next few days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/7c6720db2d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 21:02:17 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/03/four-new-pens.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/03/four-new-pens.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/monday&quot;&gt;Micro Monday&lt;/a&gt; I’ll recommend &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/zsbenke&quot;&gt;@zsbenke&lt;/a&gt; he shares interesting links and I’m trying to convince him to create a day one replacement :D&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 17:26:12 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/03/for-micro-monday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/03/for-micro-monday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished reading: &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/books/9780143109013&quot;&gt;Perennial seller &lt;/a&gt; by Ryan Holiday 📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 17:21:33 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/03/finished-reading-perennial.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/03/finished-reading-perennial.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thoughts on Parenthood 1: “I understand every adult in my life better now”. - said on FaceTime to my Uncle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 13:57:01 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/03/thoughts-on-parenthood.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/03/thoughts-on-parenthood.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“What you need to do, Peter, is stop believing all those sick people on the television and news and stop listening to those crazy people making that stuff they call music…If all you collage kids want to leave this country or burn it down, you better be mighty sure you know what you’re doing”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/006095955X/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;A Walk Across America&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started A Walk Across America (I heard about it via the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sketchnotearmy.com/blog/2018/8/27/sketchnote-army-podcast-season-05-episode-08-patrick-rhone&quot;&gt;Sketchnote Army Podcast with Patrick Rhone&lt;/a&gt;) and this line from the second chapter really struck me. I was reading the second before and had this gnawing feeling in my chest “Was the post-Vietnam US similar to today?” I can’t answer this for certain, but lines like this make me wonder if there are some echoes in our world today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 21:45:29 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/02/what-you-need.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/02/what-you-need.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Turns out two of my big complaints about DayOne V3 turn out not to be true. I &lt;strong&gt;have&lt;/strong&gt; been grandfathered into my plus scheme &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; you can now print books internationally. There are still aspects I miss about the original and I can see someone making a better rival, still I think I’ll stick with it for now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 10:46:18 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/09/01/turns-out-two.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/09/01/turns-out-two.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Built to Last </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was fifteen, my dad bough me my first guitar, a Tanglewood dreadnought style acoustic. Last year I brought it over to Poland so I could play it again. I’ve had it over half my life now, and it’s still going strong. It’s showing signs of age and breakdown but it will keep going and may well outlive me (even though it’s not really alive).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think about my guitar and other long-lasting tech when I consider most modern technology. With my recent reading of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0143109014/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;Perennial Seller&lt;/a&gt; and the upcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/apple-events/september-2018/&quot;&gt;Apple event&lt;/a&gt;, there is a lot of buzz over upgrades and the debates over what device to get. I’m looking at upgrading my phone from an iPhone SE to &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt; the iPhone X(s?). I want a smaller phone but one that has the best internals so it will keep going for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really need this upgrade, my iPhone SE still works really well, the iOS 12 beta has made it much faster and more responsive and is like a processor upgrade, and the battery still lasts a good amount of time (and could be upgraded). Despite these factors, a new iPhone is still probably the best idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife has my old iPhone 5s and its battery is not doing so well, in addition we have just become parents and I’d love her to be able to take live photos as well. I’m also worried that the security updates will eventual stop coming for the 5s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be far to Apple, their software updates do help their devices last much longer than the average phone company, and the proliferation of battery replacement recently has helped devices last longer, still I know for sure that even the latest iPhone won’t outlast me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year I bought an old hassleblad 500cm, a medium format film camera. It’s from the year I was born and it’s going strong. I can bet it will still be going strong in 30 years time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 20:30:11 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/31/built-to-last.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/31/built-to-last.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Currently reading: &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/books/9780143109013&quot;&gt;Perennial Seller &lt;/a&gt; by Ryan Holiday  📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 08:10:13 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/31/currently-reading-perennial.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/31/currently-reading-perennial.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Does Patreon’s Value Increase the More Things You Back? </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Patreon has always seemed like an interesting idea to me and I’ve backed a few groups for a couple of months at a time. For some reason I always stop. At the same time I back other site memberships. I imagine that I’d love to keep all the sites I’m a member of in one easier to manage location (patreon) and so I suspect the value of patreon for the backer increases the more things you back at the same time. Still, it’s not been enough to get me to back…yet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 08:03:15 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/31/does-patreons-value.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/31/does-patreons-value.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;affinity-publisher-beta-demo-out&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://affinity.serif.com/en-us/publisher&quot;&gt;Affinity Publisher Beta demo out&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pretty exciting to see the Affinity Publisher beta out. It’s Mac only for now but if anyone is going to create an iPad version, it’s affinity (and they’ve mentioned they will.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 14:23:58 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/30/affinity-publisher-beta.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/30/affinity-publisher-beta.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Johnnie Walker Red Rye Finish </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/773bf5a88f.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/773bf5a88f.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;height: auto;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying a new whiskey. It was a “hey you’ve got a baby” present.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 20:47:12 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/29/johnnie-walker-red.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/29/johnnie-walker-red.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A dumb nonsensical behaviour from myself. I’ve wanted to sign up as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/relayfm&quot;&gt;@relayfm&lt;/a&gt; member for a couple of years but everytime I’m about to I hit a “paradox of choice” situation. I think I want to give to every show, but there are some shows I don’t listen to so I think about choosing one show…but which one! If I could tick the shows I listen to I would (but that would be much harder to impliment). So I get caught in a mental loop and delay signing up. So today I (finally) signed up for “all the great shows”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 14:56:32 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/29/a-dumb-nonsensical.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/29/a-dumb-nonsensical.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Ideas are Cheap</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Another idea from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0143109014/?tag=minima0e-20&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;perennial seller&lt;/strong&gt; by Ryan Holiday&lt;/a&gt;, ideas are cheap, executing really matters. So many people have a &lt;em&gt;“great idea for a book”&lt;/em&gt; but a tiny fraction of those people actually even start writing (and then an even smaller fraction finish. It’s completely true and one of the key changes I made in my early twenties was moving from having ideas to trying out ideas. Later in my twenties I started getting better at finishing those same ideas and not just starting a whole host of new ones. However, that is &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; a skill I need to develop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did think of &lt;a href=&quot;https://jamesaltucher.com/2018/08/3-habits-transform-life/&quot;&gt;James Altchure’s idea factory habit (habit two)&lt;/a&gt;. He seeks to be a constantly thinking of ideas &lt;strong&gt;AND&lt;/strong&gt; reviewing them to only take action on the best ones. While ideas are cheap, we also need ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I remembered &lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=9OuG2b7V2sU&quot;&gt;Dan Aierly who described how people want to be given credit for their ideas more than the actions they take.&lt;/a&gt; I can certainly relate and I believe that’s related to why the statement that “ideas are cheap” is so tough to stomach. We want recognition for our ideas, we believe they are valuable, but in reality no one rewards you just for ideas, they reward people for carrying out their ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/e77708e0a1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 17:47:29 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/28/ideas-are-cheap.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/28/ideas-are-cheap.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the greatest little features Evernote made was the “clearly web clipper”. It was so great for saving web article, but also for general web browsing. (I still have it on my mac)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 07:42:47 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/28/one-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/28/one-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>No, you shouldn't spend 4/5th of your time marketing and 1/5th creating</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m listening to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0143109014/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;”perennial seller”&lt;/em&gt; by Ryan Holiday&lt;/a&gt; and early on he takes aim at this truism that’s been going around. spend 1/5th of your time creating and 4/5ths promoting. He said it sounds good but really if your products not up to snuff then you’re trying to generate interest in something which doesn’t matter. (Being cynical it could well be that the type of business advisor who passes on this advice knows that their audiences products aren’t that good).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway I was curious what the biggest companies ad spend to research budget was and if this might inform a better principle/ demonstrate that the 4/5th marketing idea was wrong. So what better place to start than Apple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apple-ad-spend-to-rnd&quot;&gt;Apple ad Spend to RnD&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apple’s ad spend is now not widely revealed and bundled in with its administrative costs. That’s because it’s under 10% of its expenses and so it isn’t necessary to disclose. The last available figure is from 2015 when it was $1.8 billion. Pretty high, but how did RnD compare in 2015? In fact, in 2015 RnD budget rose by $1.5 billion to aproximaately $5.9 billion. And in 2017 there was a $10 billion RnD spend target. So it’s possible that Apple spends closer to ten times as much on developing products than marketing them. Even a conservative estimate would argue they spend a reverse 4/5ths on creating and 1/5th on marketing,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;general-motors&quot;&gt;General Motors&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How about General Motors? Not a one of these modern tech companies but still a form of technology. Well the statistics for 2017 show they spend &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/261531/general-motors-advertising-spending-in-the-us/&quot;&gt;$3.24 billion&lt;/a&gt; on advertising but &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/260866/research-and-development-expenditures-of-general-motors&quot;&gt;$7.3 billion&lt;/a&gt; on Research and development. That’s just over twice as much on research than marketing. Again not the four fifths dynamic that was advised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;amazon&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon spent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.recode.net/2017/9/1/16236506/tech-amazon-apple-gdp-spending-productivity&quot;&gt;$16 billion&lt;/a&gt; on research and development last year and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/investing/2017/06/15/amazon-spends-more-on-marketing-than-wal-mart-targ.aspx&quot;&gt;$7 Billion&lt;/a&gt; on advertising in 2016. Seeing as amazon also sells products and has a movie streaming service, we could also include the &lt;a href=&quot;https://businessinsider.com.pl/amazon-video-budget-in-2017-45-billion-2017-4?utm_source=businessinsider.com&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=redirect_businessinsider_com&quot;&gt;$4.5 billion&lt;/a&gt; it spent on acquiring film rights as part of the cost of product vs marketing but regardless, Amazon also spends more on “creating” than marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion-spend-more-time-creating-than-marketing&quot;&gt;Conclusion, spend more time creating than marketing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conclusion from these companies is clear, you should spend more time creating than marketing. It’s much easier to market good products than bad ones.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 20:38:39 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/27/no-you-shouldnt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/27/no-you-shouldnt.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For some strange reason ulysses keeps crashing on my iPad Pro. Anyone got this issue or just me?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 10:15:14 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/27/for-some-strange.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/27/for-some-strange.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks for the reminders Krakow. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/9a10c2a434.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;EFA2AC59-2B52-4A38-8850-7BEA03D0D5CC.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 20:21:13 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/25/thanks-for-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/25/thanks-for-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Good link posts vs bad link post </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every now and again I come across someone who is critical of this form of micro blogging. They usually argue that all link posts are bad, but personally I’ve found it to be a mixed bag with higher and lower quality. This means there must be some factors which separate good link posts and bad link posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In truth, I think that a good link post is similar to a good blog post, it provides the reader with some for of value. Be that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;entertainment&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;education
or whatever, in every case you feel that you got value from that blog post/link post. In terms of link posts, I can identify three forms of value I get from good link posts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-discovery-via-one-link-post&quot;&gt;1. Discovery via one link post&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where a link is shared and it leads me to an article I wouldn’t have read before. In a situation like this, simply sharing the link on social media might have the same effect but the link post usually makes it stand out more in my RSS feed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-discovery-via-the-hive-mind&quot;&gt;2. Discovery via the hive mind&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where a link is shared once and it passes me by, perhaps the topic sounds boring or the title isn’t very descriptive/interesting. However, soon it seems that &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; is sharing the same links and I finally give into the pressure and try it out. In this case, it might be quote that the final person shares that makes me crack, but again it is usually the fact that something is being linked everywhere rather than how the link post actually is formatted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-commentary&quot;&gt;3. Commentary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third category is where someone takes a link but goes further, they add their unique take or insight on the story. Perhaps it is their own story or whatever, regardless, the value in this case is both the original article &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; the additional commentary. The previous two cases have value in the curation, this last one has value in the link post. That’s why I usually try and write a link post like this, one which has some additional value or insight. That because I think there is a common trait in bad link posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-same-old-same-old&quot;&gt;The same old, same old&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The common trait in bad posts is that &lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt; link post has no value. Either the link doesn’t pass on value or the commentary doesn’t. Perhaps it’s because I’ve come across the article already, the article isn’t that interesting to me, or the commentary doesn’t really add anything. In this case the more the article gets linked, the worse quality usually comes with it. It’s usually the same old talking points and I’m more likely to have read it or just not be interested in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;steal-dont-copy&quot;&gt;Steal don’t copy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another way to put it would be that you should steal (like an artist) and take some else’s link but not just copy it. Add&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;your own insight,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;your favourite quote (and why)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;an experience that was similar (or completely the opposite)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;what questions you have&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;some related links&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;something else&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So basically, make sure you give value with your linking and everyone wins. Or don’t and just write for you  and you’ll be happy anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 16:44:08 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/25/good-link-posts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/25/good-link-posts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>WWU Lecture on Tolkein’s Language and Writing</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/5NKlr0vRX34&quot;&gt;WWU lecture on Tolkein’s language and writing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a pretty fascinating 50 mins talk by Edward Vajda on how Tolkien’s love of languages impacted his writing. One of my favourite points he makes is that the names of places and their languages get more exotic the further you go from The Shire. Bree was influence by Welsh, Gondor and Rohan by Scotland and Ireland, Dwarvish has gramatically characteristics similar to Arabic and Hebrew, The East by Turkish and Hungarian languages which were associated with invaders. So basically the languages inform how you perceive those places.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 08:04:23 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/25/wwu-lecture-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/25/wwu-lecture-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After an incident yesterday I drew up a basic door protocol, I might need to add some more conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/3ad070fc08.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 07:51:52 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/25/after-an-incident.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/25/after-an-incident.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Turlaj Klopsa</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ed370b3dc1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/ed370b3dc1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/e0bab06ae3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/e0bab06ae3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;449&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; style=&quot;display: inline-block; max-height: 200px; width: auto; padding: 1px;&quot; class=&quot;sunlit_image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I needed a snack between visits to my daughter in hospital and may have found the best food truck in krakow. Veggie/vegan dumplings/meatballs with an African sauce and black rice. Adds more weight to my theory (which I probably stole) that Vegans have the tastiest food cause they have to care about flavour and can’t just dump some meat in.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 17:57:33 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/24/turlaj-klopsa.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/24/turlaj-klopsa.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Welcome to the World</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I collapsed on my bed at 2:30 on Wedneday morning after driving home from the hospital. I had been concerned that I wouldn’t be able to fall a sleep but soon my heavy eyes shut for four hours or so till my morning alarm reopened them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four hours earlier my baby girl left her hiding place and entered the world. It’s an experience which was truly mind blowing and left me speechless and frozen. I’m not sure anything could have made me properly prepared though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My daughter has entered a completely different world to the one I did just over thirty years ago. My wife and I were discussing it just the night before that she’ll see incredible things and grow up in a world so removed from our own. She’ll face new challenges (as well as some of the same old ones) and be blessed with new advantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the last few months I’ve known roughly when my daughter would arrive – though she did decide to arrive early – and with several commitments and invitations I’ve replied that I’d have to see how things are once she is here. This is continuing as she remains in Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m fully prepared for all my once existent free time to disappear in a puff of smoke. It’s certainly made me reevaluate many of the things I’ve been doing. Many of them just don’t see important in the grand scheme of things now, others seem more fun. It’s a big part of my change in writing and embracing micro.blog further as well as enjoying drawing and analogue tools more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, my plans don’t focus that much on me anymore. I’ll be adapting to her needs and wants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t wait to learn more about her and what she’s interested in.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 12:40:33 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/24/welcome-to-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/24/welcome-to-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Inside J.R.R. Tolkien’s Notebooks, a Glimpse of the Master Philologist at Work</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/13/books/review/jrr-tolkien-lord-of-the-rings-elvish-language.html&quot;&gt;Inside J.R.R. Tolkien’s Notebooks, a Glimpse of the Master Philologist at Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tolkien was the first philologist to establish such a network of evolving dialects that derive from one another “by slowly accumulating changes and divergences in form across time from a common ancestor species.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t lie that this hits me in three directions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tolkien&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Languages&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;notebooks
I found it fascinating his work to include changes between dialects overtime. I’ve read a bit on the languages in Tolkein’s world and the influences of real world languages on Elvish (particularly Welsh on Sindarin) but I hadn’t paid attention to the evolution of these languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thecramped.com/inside-j-r-r-tolkiens-notebooks-a-glimpse-of-the-master-philologist-at-work-the-new-york-times/&quot;&gt;the cramped&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:15:10 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/24/inside-jrr-tolkiens.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/24/inside-jrr-tolkiens.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;New Craft beer (well new to me) in local shop with a local connect. Let’s give this a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/e86b318906.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 18:38:56 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/23/new-craft-beer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/23/new-craft-beer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;How to do a strength or core workout with the Apple Watch ⌚️💪 &lt;a href=&quot;http://ipadguild.com/how-to-do-a-strength-or-core-workout-on-the-apple-watch/&quot;&gt;iPad guild&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 10:00:38 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/22/how-to-do.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/22/how-to-do.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As I thought, the latest DayOne update removes my precious, precious plus account so I now have to pay for a subscription or use the basic plan ☹️ I kind of miss DayOne classic. Audio recording could be nice though.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 06:40:27 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/22/as-i-thought.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/22/as-i-thought.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Can you draw a face with just vertical lines? 🤔 ✏️</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday evening I suddenly had a random idea*, &lt;em&gt;could I draw a face with just vertical lines?&lt;/em&gt; I grabbed my iPad and Apple pencil and gave it a go to find out that I could indeed draw a face with just verticals lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried a few combinations and the decided I had gone as far as I could do I’d try horizontal lines to see the difference. I started drawing and again reached the end after about five variations. I was about to call it quits with a warm glow on my face when I suddenly realised. &lt;em&gt;“Vertical lines can be hair!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly a whole host of new options were open to me as hair, then beards and more facial hair became a possibility. Then I realised ears could be shown with vertical lines and even piercings. I had given up to easily and almost missed out on a whole world of extra possibilities by not spending more time thinking and experimenting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously drawing a face with just vertical lines isn’t exactly a revolution or really something any of us will need to do on a day to day basis but it was fun and the main lesson —to not give up easily and keep exploring an idea — is very useful for everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*I believe this idea was a synthesis of practicing faces based of Activities from &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/Rohdesign&quot;&gt;@Rohdesign&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://austinkleon.com&quot;&gt;Austin Kleon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/19dbf43d8f.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;372&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/a820c99a7e.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;201&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/3812ca518f.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;306&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/b693a80639.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 18:26:01 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/21/can-you-draw.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/21/can-you-draw.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Day 3 📷&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/fcf9510981.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;7587C563-5423-4E2D-A2DB-427B442F4392.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 17:52:38 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/21/155238.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/21/155238.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;read-more-books-&quot;&gt;Read More Books 📚&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A reminder from myself yesterday. Books are rewarding and I should read more. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/9e4518fb93.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;C23B8CB7-A57A-487E-B30E-9C231127B251.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 08:01:33 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/21/read-more-books.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/21/read-more-books.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pocketcasts has chapters support. Nice 😎&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 07:34:02 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/21/pocketcasts-has-chapters.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/21/pocketcasts-has-chapters.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Writing is self-help, because “we’re writing to help ourselves.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://austinkleon.com/2018/08/19/self-help-as-oxymoron/&quot;&gt;Self-Help as oxymoron,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Austin Kleon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 18:30:45 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/20/writing-is-selfhelp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/20/writing-is-selfhelp.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Micro &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/Monday&quot;&gt;@Monday&lt;/a&gt; :&lt;/strong&gt;  totally has to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/gr36&quot;&gt;@gr36&lt;/a&gt; well worth following.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 17:54:40 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/20/micro-monday-totally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/20/micro-monday-totally.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>5 great newsletters ✉️</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve signed up to far too many newsletters in the past. Some have been great for a while and then warn thing and others weren’t even that great at the start. Here are five which have stood my test of time (in no particular order)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pjrvs.com&quot;&gt;Paul Jarvis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://club.macstories.net&quot;&gt;Club Macstories&lt;/a&gt; (paid)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://austinkleon.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;Austin Kleon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rohdesign.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;Mike Rhode&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cjchilvers.com/subscribe/&quot;&gt;CJ Chilvers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Share yours (you don’t have to share five)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 17:19:33 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/20/great-newsletters.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/20/great-newsletters.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;day-2-black-and-white&quot;&gt;Day 2 black and white&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/c6d6e2e770.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A5FFC737-4938-425C-8F00-397835BD5B8D.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 07:41:11 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/20/day-black-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/20/day-black-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just finished the show notes for the final guest episode of the sketchnote army podcast season 5. Spoiler alert 🚨 It’s a great one.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 20:07:18 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/19/just-finished-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/19/just-finished-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>A Commonplace (book/blog)</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever stumbled upon an idea that moved you into action? This last week I did in a minor way after listening to an episode of the sketchnote army podcast with Austin Kleon. In that episode he mentioned the way he was using his notebooks and within a day, I had picked up a new notebook to experiment. Perhaps this idea will inspire you into action as well. Or maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;creating-a-commonplace-book&quot;&gt;Creating a commonplace book&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Austin shared how he had started carrying a pocket notebook and logging various elements during the day. Later he’d go back over those pages and highlight the key items and ideas. Eventually, they might turn into a blog post or a book.
I had heard him talk about similar notebooking techniques before when he called it a &lt;strong&gt;commonplace book.&lt;/strong&gt; This inspired me to go out, buy a &lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt; a6-ish size moleskine and record. I had already been doing something similar at my work desk on pages of A4, but the pocket book had the advantage of being with me not only at my desk but also on the train, when in bed and basically everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There’s something charming about keeping an analogue notebook in an increasingly digital world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/4f2175887b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;commonplace book quote&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-digital-commonplace&quot;&gt;the digital commonplace&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, the natural extension of this new notebook was to start sharing some extracts online, specifically on micro.blog. It reminded me of the charm of early blogging. When it wasn’t so serious, when you didn’t need a specific goal or career from it and mistakes were useful and a sign of growth. You didn’t (and don’t) have to present yourself as an expert in something you just started out in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This digital commonplace book or &lt;em&gt;adversersia&lt;/em&gt; had some obvious advantages such as linking to music or videos online as well as sharing items. &lt;strong&gt;Even though analogue tools have a charm, digital tools provide some extra functions&lt;/strong&gt;. Of course, we don’t have to choose one or another, we can have both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://tenor.com/view/why-not-both-both-yay-celebrate-two-gif-5620885&quot; alt=&quot;por que no los dos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-need-to-dig-deeper&quot;&gt;The need to dig deeper&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keeping this notebook has made me really appreciate deeper content and devalue shallow, entertainment focused items. I want to be clear here, I’m not saying entertainment is wrong, I’m not saying you should do or feel the same, this has been my reaction. 
When reading a book or something of greater depth, material is provided for the commonplace book. A quote here, an idea there, a beautiful graphic to copy. When the material is shallow, repeating the same talking points, then it’s much rarer for my book to see any difference. I’ve almost gamed myself to want to read more books than blogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had actually been feeling guilty or &lt;em&gt;FOMO&lt;/em&gt; about not being to keep up with all the micropodcast that have been starting up (especially with starting one myself. How can I expect people to listen to my own if I don’t listen to theirs?) but this notebook has helped me deal with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We can’t do every great things, and trying to have it all, result in having nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By trying to keep up with all these podcasts and blogs, I’m missing out on reading great books. So I’m making a commitment, to fill my adversaria, to read great books and go deeper.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 16:38:48 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/18/a-commonplace-bookblog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/18/a-commonplace-bookblog.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I keep wanting to “like” things here…but I don’t want to favourite them. I’ve been trained not to comment but star on social media and it’s not easy to untrain yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 15:51:37 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/18/i-keep-wanting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/18/i-keep-wanting.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Drafts for Mac 🖥 </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://forums.getdrafts.com/t/drafts-for-mac-status-update/2276&quot;&gt;Drafts for Mac Status Update - Drafts Community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yes, Drafts is coming to the Mac. Much of the groundwork for this release was done while building the Drafts 5 update. We are now in the process of building the Mac user interface and Mac-specific features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although I’m very much an iOS user, having the option of drafts on the Mac will be great. Of course, I’m writing this in drafts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 20:14:29 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/17/drafts-for-mac.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/17/drafts-for-mac.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;thank-you-for-today-by-death-cab-for-cutiesongwhipcomalbumdea&quot;&gt;[Thank You for Today by Death Cab for Cutie](&lt;a href=&quot;https://songwhip.com/album/death-cab-for-cutie/thank-you-for-today&quot;&gt;songwhip.com/album/dea…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Death Cab album. 
Nice&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 14:53:13 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/17/thank-you-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/17/thank-you-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pay every debt as if God wrote the bill - Ralph Waldo Emerson (playing with my common book) 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/4f2175887b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;25692641-3365-4730-9BEE-A33EDB7454FC.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 14:26:11 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/17/pay-every-debt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/17/pay-every-debt.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Day 1 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/a8d26788bb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;769EED5E-40F6-4167-A21F-9F629A6F7C2F.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 08:07:49 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/17/day.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/17/day.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Idea for a relay crossover episode Federico and John Siracusa talk pasta workflows. Call me &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ismh&quot;&gt;@ismh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 17:49:26 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/16/idea-for-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/16/idea-for-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pca.st/IXlA&quot;&gt;SongExploder: Christine and the Queens - Doesn’t matter&lt;/a&gt;
I love the behind the scenes glimps you get from Song Exploder and Christine and the Queens are a great act to find out about. A really interesting song too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 10:43:22 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/16/songexploder-christine-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/16/songexploder-christine-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My hypercritical and PCalc T-shirt’s arrived 😎&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/b03c3308b1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 17:48:11 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/14/my-hypercritical-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/14/my-hypercritical-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>It’s Just Not for Me</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, it happened. A company I really like released a product that I have no interest in buying to the extent that I don’t even want to buy it to support them. I hope it sells well but it’s just not for me. I’ve seen this happen before and after that point every product a company made “wasn’t for me” so I’m really hoping this is a one off.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 16:00:56 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/14/its-just-not.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/14/its-just-not.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I finally took &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/gr36&quot;&gt;@gr36&lt;/a&gt; ‘s suggestion and moved all my podcasts to Pocketcasts and started a big clean up. The good and bad news is there are too many good podcasts at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 11:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/14/i-finally-took.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/14/i-finally-took.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Icro now has image upload. This makes me happy. Micro.blog is coming along nicely.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 07:49:03 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/14/icro-now-has.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/14/icro-now-has.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Got a couple new pens to play with after discovering a great stationary shop in Krakow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/116bef1456.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 16:59:30 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/13/got-a-couple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/13/got-a-couple.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sunday morning lettering practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://chrisjwilson.me/uploads/2018/6ad50d5309.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 07:27:27 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/12/sunday-morning-lettering.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/12/sunday-morning-lettering.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Moving webhosts can really be a pain (but at least I’ve finished).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 17:50:56 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/08/11/moving-webhosts-can.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/08/11/moving-webhosts-can.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
