<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Christopher Wilson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ChrisJWilson&quot;&gt;@ChrisJWilson on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 07:50:27 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 07:50:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Why are there “delux albums” on Apple Music?</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://benjaminmayo.co.uk/apple-music-first-impressions&quot;&gt;Apple Music First Impressions - Benjamin Mayo&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The archaic concept of a standard album and a deluxe album are still in use. It’s a digitisation of a physical CD inventory, not a modern reset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ben’s completely right here. It’s a pain in Apple Music to go searching for certain music. The fact that singles get mixed in with Albums in a pain in the neck.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 07:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/02/17/apple-music-first.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/02/17/apple-music-first.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>a different -kind of- writing process</title>
        
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Write 1st draft, it’s too long, &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;write second draft, it’s long, &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;write third draft, okay we’re getting somewhere, but maybe we need to start again, &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;write fourth draft, okay we’re heading in the right direction now. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Re-read fourth version, cut useless words, rephrase sections, cut a paragraph that isn’t needed, add a new one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not my normal writing process. Normally I either write in one go and then edit &lt;strong&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt; I write once, delete and then write again. This time I’m writing for someone else’s publication and there’s so much I could add. That’s what I realised on the second draft, I could say more. But the truth is, the reader wants something for them, they don’t care about the aspects I find interesting or the fine details. They want the interesting take away or idea for them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why I’m taking my time, and I’ve not even finished yet&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 15:56:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/02/16/a-different-kind.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/02/16/a-different-kind.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Turtles all the way down</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the things I’ve found really strange on the internet are the sort of “pyramid” schemes. You know, the internet marketer, who teaches you internet marketing, so you too can become an internet marketer, in internet marketing. Or the writer, who writes books, on how to write books…about writing books. Or the YouTuber who makes YouTube videos about how you can make YouTube videos. Obviously not everyone who does internet marketing or teachers internet marketing &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; does internet marketing or &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; has experience in this field, but there are plenty of other “fake it till you make it” folk, and it’s telling when they seem to produce people who do the exact same thing (just less successfully). 
I’ll add, that It’s also why I find the sketchnote community concerning sometimes. Some people only seem to share sketchnotes of how to sketchnote…and that’s pretty weird. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/02/15/turtles-all-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/02/15/turtles-all-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People give Evernote a lot of stick, but it’s improved a lot recently…well, it’s stopped bugging me about WorkChat…so that’s a massive improvement. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 19:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/02/14/people-give-evernote.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/02/14/people-give-evernote.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://brooksreview.net/2018/02/thoughts-on-new-ipads/&quot;&gt;Thoughts On New iPads -&amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/ben&quot;&gt;@ben&lt;/a&gt; makes some good points here about the orientation apple sees iPads being used in. Personally, I used my iPad Air in portrait more than my Pro because the Smart Keyboard can &lt;strong&gt;only&lt;/strong&gt; be used in landscape. And that’s a shame.  &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 10:21:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/02/13/thoughts-on-new.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/02/13/thoughts-on-new.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Oh Hi there Micro.Blog</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So after this week &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.relay.fm/mpu/417&quot;&gt;Mac Power users podcast&lt;/a&gt; I finally got round to signing up for Micro.Blog. I had been meaning to do so for a bit, especially after seeing people like &lt;a href=&quot;http://decoding.io/&quot;&gt;Zsolt Benke at decoding&lt;/a&gt; using the service on their own site. However I wondered if I should use it on my own site or whatever. In the end, I signed up for a Micro.blog blog as I wanted to help support the service as well. Paying $5 seems like a good way to do so and solved my overthinking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why did I sign up in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-increasing-announance-at-social-media-twitter&quot;&gt;My increasing announance at Social Media (twitter)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve increasingly felt that social media is very “meh”. I hate what Facebook has become as it increasingly tried to grab my attention with cheap tricks and tracks everything I do (no matter if I try to stop that). Twitter too isn’t perfect with its lack of efforts to stop trolling and abuse. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-announance-at-blogging&quot;&gt;My announance at blogging&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Likewise I’m fed up of the “professional blogging culture”. There are so many “have tos” with blogging now like:&lt;br /&gt;
- write long posts
- have links
- be helpful
- only show the good sides
- no link posts
- be on a single focus topic
And so on and so on. 
All great advice if you want to make money, but as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cjchilvers.com/blog/welcome-back-blogging&quot;&gt;CJ Chilvers says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“one is a business model, one is a life model” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what I’m hoping for in this site. Somewhere to play, somewhere to create and somewhere to be unprofessional. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 09:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://chrisjwilson.me/2018/02/13/oh-hi-there.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ChrisJWilson.micro.blog/2018/02/13/oh-hi-there.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
